Abhijeet Singh

Software Developer based in Vancouver, BC. Crafting engaging experiences for the Internet.

With a creative approach to development, I add intuitiveness and life to my work. Building beautiful interfaces and performant backend applications for professional, academic, and personal projects. Outside of programming, I enjoy making 3d renders and animations.

■ abhijeetsinghmain@gmail.com

+1 604 339 8625

abjt.dev

in linkedin.com/in/abjt14

github.com/abjt14

⇔ codepen.io/abjt14

▲ artstation.com/abjt

Experience

AvenueHQ | Vancouver, Canada

Junior Full-Stack Engineer | Mar 2022 - Aug 2022

- Worked on a digital marketing tool for realtors through North America.
- Built a performant client facing API-driven application in React.
- Used Laravel and SQL to build fast, efficient and scalable databases and APIs.
- Collaborated across internal teams to clarify requirements, explore issues, provide updates, and present discoveries.

Outlined.co | Bangalore, India

Software Engineer | Sept 2019 - Oct 2020

- Developed and maintained the company's product marketing website and flagship design platform using FabricJS and Laravel.
- Built a PDF to HTML canvas converter using JavaScript and Shell Scripting to import and export design files on the browser.
- Implemented API Integration for data storage, social media interaction, text sentimental analysis, and stock image services.

Education

Langara College | Vancouver, Canada

Post-Graduate Diploma | 2020-2022 Web and Mobile App Design and Development

Manipal University Jaipur | Jaipur, India

Bachelor of Technology | 2015-2019 Information Technology

Technical Skills

HTML5

JavaScript

CSS

- ML5 TypeScript
 - React
 - · Neaci
 - Svelte
 - Vue
 - React Native
- Next JS
- Node
- Laravel
- MySQL
- lative MongoDB
 - GraphQL
- · Shell Scripting
- Git
- Figma